nice to meet you.
初めまして
初 めまして
Your voice is cute.
声かわいいね
That's what everyone says.
みんなそう言うんだよね
This is a hotel, but I just came here.
ここホテルだけど、 来たってことでさ
In front of the camera, etc.
これカメラの前でね、とか
Shall we talk for a moment?
ちょっとお話ししよっか
Do you like traveling?
旅行好きなの?
What's the best place you've been to so far?
今までにさ、 行った中で一番良かったときはどこ?
What was good?
どこが良かったの?
Hokkaido?
北海道?
What was good?
どこが良かった?
I'm glad I went to Hokkaido.
北海道に行って良かったな
It was more fun that way.
その方がお楽しかったです
It's cute.
かわいいね
Do you go often?
結構行くの?
To Hokkaido.
北海道に
So, where do you want to go next?
じゃあさ、次どっか行きたいとかある?
Next...
次は...
Kamakura!
鎌倉!
Why Kamakura?
なんで鎌倉なの?
I want to go.
行ってみたい
Do you want to go?
行ってみたい?
So, are you a domestic person?
じゃあ、国内派なの?
I'm a domestic person.
国内派なんだ
I see.
なるほどね
What do you want to go to after Kamakura?
鎌倉の次に行きたいってことは?
sickle
鎌
倉?
Oh, nothing special.
あ、 別に
I want to go.
行きたいってこと
Singapore.
シンガポール
It splashed.
はねたね
You broke the contract.
違約したね
Do you want to go to Singapore after Kamakura?
鎌倉から次、シンガポール行きたいの?
What is Singapore?
シンガポールは何で?
Is there anything you want to see?
何 か見たいものとかあるの?
Looks like fun.
楽しそう
Does it look like fun?
楽しそうなの?
Have you ever been abroad?
海外とか行ったことあるの?
I've never been there.
行ったことないんです
Singapore might be your first overseas trip.
初海外がシンガポールになるかもしれないのね
It's stylish.
おしゃれだ
So, I like living in Japan, but I'm also a little interested in overseas.
じゃあ国内が好きだけど、 海 外もちょっと興味あるよって
Even now, things are difficult.
今でもいろいろ大変だからね
The importance.
大事性が
I have to go before something happens.
何かならないうちに行かないとね
My hobby is traveling.
趣味は旅行が好きだ
What do you do on your days off?
お休みの日とかは何してるの?
Do you like reading books?
本読むの好きなの?
What kind of books do you read?
どういう本読むの?
A novel or something...
小説とか、何かその...
What do you say...
何て言うんだ、その...
It's like beforehand.
事前みたいなさ
novel.
小説
What is the genre?
ジャンルは?
The genre is mystery.
ジャンルはミステリー
I like mysteries.
ミステリーが好きなんだ
It's quite a mystery to read difficult books like that.
結構そういう 難しい本とか読むの ミステリー
Or something.
とか
nice.
いい ね
My hobby is traveling, and I usually read books and enjoy the outdoors.
旅行が趣味で 普段は本読んでって アウトドアとか アウトドア
And the indoor part both have a great aura.
と インドアの部分 両方もオーラしてるね
nice.
いいね
Your skin is so white.
めちゃめちゃ肌白いね
Are you traveling?
旅行行ってる?
I'm going.
行ってます
Are you out?
外出てる?
Yeah.
うん
Are you doing something?
何かやってんの?
Like beauty, like getting whiter skin.
美容みたいな、肌白くなるみたいな
It's originally that white.
元々でその 白さなんだ
I might have turned into a woman of today's world.
今世の女性的に 回したかもしれない
It's naturally whitening.
元々美白なんだね
What are you doing now?
今 何されてるんですか?
I'm a student.
学生です
Student.
学生さん
Teaching today?
今日は教学?
Women's college?
女子大?
It's teaching.
教学です
So you have a boyfriend, right?
じゃあ彼氏いるでしょ?
I'm not there.
いないです
Are you not there?
いないの?
picture?
え?
Are there people who don't have boyfriends in university teaching?
大学の教学で 彼氏いない人とかいるの?
I'm here.
いますよ
Aren't there lots of encounters?
出会いとかいっぱいあるんじゃないの?
You'll be invited to a blind date, right?
合コンとか誘われるでしょ?
No.
ないです
Isn't there?
ないの?
Have you never been?
いたことないの?
picture?
え?
You're lying a little bit, aren't you?
ちょっと嘘ついてるでしょ?
I'm not lying.
嘘 ついてないです
Really?
本当に?
You're going to get hit with something, right?
なんぱとかされるでしょ?
It's not.
じゃないです
What would you do if something happened?
仮になんぱされたらどうする?
follow?
ついていく?
Basically, I don't do things like bang nuts.
基本的には バンナットみたいなのしない
of?
の?
Can I believe it?
信 じていいの?
Only people you've loved so far?
今まで好きな人だけ?
It's like you're drawn to that smile.
その笑顔に吸い込むそうだもんね
Is there no one you like now?
今好きな人はいないの?
I'm not there.
いないです
Do you think about love itself?
恋愛自体とか思うの?
now.
今は
If there's a good person.
いい人いれば
Currently recruiting.
募集中と
What's going on?
何事か
I would like to add a little summary section.
ちょっと概要欄貼っとくんでしたい
Recruitment starts here.
ここに募集開始募集です
please.
お願いします
I'll paste it.
貼っときます
I see.
なるほどね
So, what do you study at school?
で、学校は 勉強は何?
What series?
何系?
That's why I love books.
だから本好きなんだ
I see.
なるほどね
My hobbies live my studies.
趣 味が 学業に生きてるんだ
I see.
なるほど
nice.
いいね
That's why I write my own books and just read them.
だから自分で本書いたりとか 読むだけで
Senda to read.
読むせんだ
I'm studying humanities.
文系で勉強してますと
What are your dreams for the future and what kind of company do you want to work for?
将来の夢とか、どういう会社に働きたいとか
Is it a company or a profession?
企業か、職業か
I want to work at a travel agency.
旅行会社で働きたい
Is it a travel agency?
旅行会社だったり?
I love traveling.
好きだもんね、旅行ね
It's a hobby trip.
趣味旅行だもんね
It's a trip.
旅行だしね
Well then, something like that.
じゃ、なんかね
Well, I heard about the savings.
まあ、貯金のこと聞いたんで
I want to hear about the past.
昔のこととか 聞きたいな
Well, it was during my student days.
まあ、学生時代さ
When I was a student, I think I'm a student now.
学生時代ってか、今学生だと思うけど
Did you even do any club activities?
その1個も今さ、 部活とかやってたの?
I was doing it.
やってました
What were you doing?
何やってたの?
Youth learning.
青少学
Oh, that's cool.
ああ、ぽいわ
Can I guess?
当てていい?
flute.
フルート
different?
違う?
what?
何?
What's the answer?
答え何?
Horn.
ホルン
Seriously?
マジで?
The first thing that came to mind was the horn.
ホルンが一番頭に浮かんだんだよ
I thought it was safe to say that it was a flute.
無難なところでフルートって言ってたんだけど
Is it a horn?
ホルンなの?
Can I blow it with air now?
今エアーで吹いてもらっていいですか?
Okay.
いいよ
Once in the air.
一回、エアーで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Okay, how long have you been doing that?
結構、それはどれくらいやってたの?
Medium to high.
中高
Did you attend middle school and high school?
中高やってたの?
About 6 years.
6年くらい
That's serious.
ガチじゃん
Aren't you doing this at university now?
今、大学でもやってないの?
I haven't done it.
やってない
If it's about 6 years old, it's quite heavy.
6年くらいだと結構、重いんだよね
Try it with air.
エアーでやってみてよ
I don't want it to get too hard.
硬くなりすぎていいな
Don't you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いないんだっけ?
Do you feel like you met a good person?
いい人いたって感じか
If I found a good person, I could have a boyfriend.
もし、いい人いて彼氏ができましたと
Where do you want to go?
どこに行きたい?
Where do you want to go on your first date?
初デートどこに行きたい?
Aquarium.
水族館
Aquarium?
水族館?
I see.
なるほど
What do you want to see at an aquarium?
水族館で何が見たいの?
Is it income?
いるか所得なの?
魚
That's right.
そうだよね
Well then, tell me what your ideal date plan is.
じゃあさ、 今、理想のデートプランみたいなの教えて
For example, let's go to an aquarium.
例えば、水族館行くじゃん
When I go to the aquarium, I eat food.
水族館行ったらご飯食べるじゃん
After that?
その後は?
bye bye.
バイバイ
On our first date, we went to an aquarium and said goodbye.
初デートは水族館行ってバイバイ
Went to the aquarium, had lunch, and said it was fun.
水族館行ってご飯食べて、 楽しかったねって
Bye bye.
バイ バイって
Boyfriend, let's spend some time together.
彼氏はさ、 もうちょっと一緒にいようよ
Don't want to give it back?
返したくない?
In the flow.
流れに
If it's someone you like, that's fine.
好きな人だったらね、 いいもんね
Did you feel less nervous after hearing so many things?
い ろいろ聞いたからさ、 緊張ほぐれた?
Well, I'm going to take a quick shower.
じゃあちょっとシャワー浴びてくるから
Please wait.
待っててね
Oh, you're so relaxed.
あ、めっちゃリラックスしてんじゃん
The tension has really eased.
緊張めっちゃほぐれてんじゃん
Good
よかったよ
It was so hot.
かった
It's no good when I see it.
ダ メだな見たら
Because it was beautiful.
綺麗綺麗したからさ
I don't know what to do.
どうしていいか分かんないよね
Because it was cute.
可愛かったからさ
Is that what you mean?
そういう意味?
get nervous.
緊張する
get nervous?
緊張する?
What is this?
これ何でしょ?
This is how it is.
こうしたらさ
You can't see me kissing, right?
キスしてとか見えないでしょ?
nostalgic?
懐かしい?
Just a little more
もうちょっとだけから
hey.
ね
I like your style.
ス タイルいいよね
Good cup?
いいカップ?
That's a nice cup.
いいカップだね
You thought I'd say that now.
言うと思ったでしょ今
15時間
I don't like it.
嫌だ
picture?
え?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ
How tall are you?
身長いくつくらい?
That's right.
だよね
It's really thin.
めっちゃ細いよね
I would hate it if she were like this.
嫌だな彼女はこんなだったら
It's smooth.
すべすべだね
It's white.
白いね
Where are you going?
どこ行ってる?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
why?
なんで?
It's long and kind of embarrassing.
長くてなんか恥ずかしいのあるね
Sujima.
スジマ
Come on.
おいで
Then there you go.
じゃあそこでさ
Can you kneel?
膝立ちできる?
Kneel.
膝立ち
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
please.
お願い
together.
一緒に
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Together together together.
一緒一緒一緒
5 seconds 5 seconds 5 seconds.
5秒5秒5秒
5 seconds.
5秒
Look, look.
ほらほら
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Good.
よいしょ
picture?
え?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Have you slept all day?
一 日眠ってる?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I fell asleep.
眠っちゃった
Put your feet up.
足を上げてさ
Put your hands behind your back.
手を後ろにつける
Get on your knees.
膝ついて